<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Paso Robles Waste &amp; Recycle</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Paso Robles Waste &amp; Recycle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 09:27:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Residential</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/residential/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 09:27:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/residential/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;service:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;Service&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start or change your service, please &lt;a href=&#34;https://pasorobleswastedisposal.onlineportal.us.com/User/Login?ReturnUrl=%2f&#34;&gt;sign up / log in.&lt;/a&gt; All residential accounts receive weekly automated pickup and include organic waste and commingle curbside recycling services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;containers-a-id-containers-a:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;Containers &lt;a id=&#34;Containers&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may choose the container size that best fits your waste needs. You may change your service size any time by &lt;a href=&#34;https://pasorobleswastedisposal.onlineportal.us.com/User/Login?ReturnUrl=%2f&#34;&gt;logging in&lt;/a&gt; to your account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;instructions:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;INSTRUCTIONS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep lids closed&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent attracting flies, birds, rats and other pests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent lightweight waste from being blown out of containers and littering neighborhoods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent unpleasant odors during warm weather&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent rain water from pooling inside the containers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent over-full container charges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use only the containers provided by Paso Robles Waste &amp;amp; Recycle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use only the containers provided by Paso Robles Waste &amp;amp; Recycle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No hazardous materials such as oil, pesticides, paint or cleaners. No putrescible waste like food scraps, diapers, etc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Place bins at curb no later than 6am on your pick-up day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintain three feet of space between bins and cars&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recycling:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;Recycling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View our list of recyclable materials and check back for updates. Our list increases as recycling technology improves. We offer weekly curbside pick-up of household commingled recyclables (blue cart) and organic waste (green cart) for all residential customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;contamination:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;CONTAMINATION&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clean organic waste is a must. Our organic waste truck has a video camera to monitor organic waste container contents as it is emptied. Containers contaminated with trash will receive a service charge of $7.40 per incident. Repeat offenders will have containers removed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;motor-oil:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;MOTOR OIL&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy, convenient and free. Call our office at (805) 238-2381 to schedule a pick-up of your used motor oil. We will provide you with a 15-quart capacity oil container and an oil filter bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;batteries-and-electronic-waste-a-id-batteries-2f-e-waste:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;BATTERIES AND ELECTRONIC WASTE&lt;a id=&#34;batteries-%2f-e-waste&#34;/&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The San Luis Obispo Integrated Waste Management Authority (IWMA) had provided us with containers to accept your household batteries and electronic waste, which are located at our office. You can drop off your materials Monday–Friday, 8am–5pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Batteries in the landfill present many health and environmental risks. By recycling these products, we will be cutting down on the amount of natural resources needed to produce the never-ending supply of batteries that our society has come to depend on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_909&#34;&gt;&lt;strong id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_908&#34;&gt;Battery Facts (www.epa.gov)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Americans purchase nearly 3 billion dry-cell batteries every year to power radios, toys, cellular phones, watches, laptop computers, and portable power tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inside a battery, heavy metals react with chemical electrolyte to produce the battery’s power&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wet-cell batteries, which contain a liquid electrolyte, commonly power automobiles, boats, or motorcycles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nearly 99 million wet-cell lead-acid car batteries are manufactured each year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mercury was phased out of certain types of batteries in conjunction with the “Mercury-Containing and Rechargeable Battery Management Act,” passed in 1996&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recycling batteries keeps heavy metals out of landfills and the air. Recycling saves resources because recovered plastic and metals can be used to make new batteries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_909&#34;&gt;&lt;strong id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_908&#34;&gt;Battery Facts (www.epa.gov)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_602&#34;&gt;Rechargeable batteries are a great way to cut down on the amount of batteries that end up in our waste stream. It is possible for one rechargeable battery to do the work of hundreds of single-use batteries. Once a rechargeable battery no longer holds a charge, it is best to recycle it so that it never ends up in our landfills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;fluorescent-lamp-and-tube-recycling:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;FLUORESCENT LAMP AND TUBE RECYCLING&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The San Luis Obispo IWMA has provided us with containers to accept your household fluorescent lamps and tubes at our office. You can drop off your materials Monday–Friday, 8am–5pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For information about safely recycling or disposing of fluorescent lamps and tubes, visit the California Integrated Waste Management Board website, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.calrecycle.ca.gov/&#34;&gt;CalRecycle.CA.gov.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;rates-billing:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;Rates &amp;amp; Billing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To view your bill, please visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://pasorobleswastedisposal.onlineportal.us.com/User/Login?ReturnUrl=%2f0&#34;&gt;Pay Bill&lt;/a&gt;. Payment methods accepted are cash, check, and VISA/MasterCard. We also offer recurring monthly ACH or VISA/MasterCard payments in addition to e-Invoices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To view current rates, please &lt;a href=&#34;https://pasorobleswastedisposal.onlineportal.us.com/User/Login?ReturnUrl=%2f&#34;&gt;sign up / log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-lg&#34; data-toggle=&#34;modal&#34; data-target=&#34;#rateModal&#34; href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/modal/residential-rates/&#34;&gt;
      Additional Information
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;modal fade&#34; id=&#34;rateModal&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34; role=&#34;dialog&#34; aria-labelledby=&#34;myModalLabel&#34; style=&#34;display: none;&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;modal-dialog&#34; role=&#34;document&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;modal-content&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;modal-header&#34;&gt;
        &lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;close&#34; data-dismiss=&#34;modal&#34; aria-label=&#34;Close&#34;&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;×&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;h4 class=&#34;modal-title&#34; id=&#34;myModalLabel&#34;&gt;Rates&lt;/h4&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;modal-body&#34;&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;modal-footer&#34;&gt;
        &lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-default&#34; data-dismiss=&#34;modal&#34;&gt;Close&lt;/button&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;extra-services:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;Extra Services&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;bag-tags:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;BAG TAGS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have more trash than what fits into your regular service, you can buy tags for $XX each by calling our office at (805) 238-2381. These tags will cover a 32 gallon container whether it is a box, bag or can (50 lbs. or less).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rent-a-bin-service:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;RENT-A-BIN SERVICE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer 3- and 4-yard temporary bin service. You can order a bin any time you have a larger-than-normal volume of garbage to dispose of. These bins are great for home remodeling and construction projects. &lt;a href=&#34;https://paso-waste-site.squarespace.com/rent-a-bin&#34;&gt;Learn More &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;in-yard-service:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;IN-YARD SERVICE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have difficulty getting your container to the curb, you can sign up for in-yard service. Your regular driver will come into your yard to retrieve your container, empty it, and then return it to your yard. In many cases we are able to offer this service at no additional charge. All you need is a valid doctor’s note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;bulky-items:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;BULKY ITEMS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can collect bulky items. Please call our office at (805) 238-2381 for an estimate. Bulky items include appliances, furniture, mattresses, any over-sized item that will not fit into your container. Read below for more information about our annual Clean-Up Week for bulky items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;holiday-schedule:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;Holiday Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our company runs a regular service schedule 51 weeks a year. We do not change our regular pickup schedule for any holidays except Christmas Day. During Christmas week, service on or after Christmas Day is delayed by one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;christmas-week-service-schedule:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;CHRISTMAS WEEK SERVICE SCHEDULE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;table class=&#34;christmas-week&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular Service Day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/th&gt;
            &lt;th&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Day for Christmas Week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Monday&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Monday, December 21, 2015&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Tuesday&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Tuesday, December 22, 2015&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Wednesday&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Wednesday, December 23, 2015&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Thursday&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Thursday, December 24, 2015&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Friday&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Saturday, December 26, 2015&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Service will return to the regular schedule starting December 28, 2015.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;christmas-tree-pick-up:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;CHRISTMAS TREE PICK-UP&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For no additional charge, you can place your whole undecorated tree at the curb on your regular service day between December 28, 2015 through January 8, 2016. We will be operating an additional truck that will be picking up just the Christmas trees. If you have any questions or concerns please call our office at (805) 238-2381.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_895&#34;&gt;&lt;strong id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_894&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have your tree at the curb on your regular pick-up day no later than 6:00am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove all decorations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove the stand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not cut it up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure it is visible to the drivers (it’s best to place it next to your trash can, but not blocking it)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We won’t accept flocked trees for recycling (you’ll need to cut it up and place it in your trash can)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will not collect trees with decorations or stands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-will-not-collect-trees-with-decorations-or-stands:8bb510895c15cdb2b4b1952437a3c932&#34;&gt;We will not collect trees with decorations or stands&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This annual June event allows each single family residence to place a maximum of seven (7) items of bulk household waste for curbside pick up during the clean-up event &lt;strong&gt;FOR FREE!&lt;/strong&gt; Bulk household waste means all discarded household waste matter which is too large to be placed in a covered container including, but not limited to, vehicle tires and/or wheels, furniture, appliances, discarded carpets, discarded mattresses, discarded electronic equipment, residential wastes (including wood waste, tree branches, scrap wood) and similar large items produced from residential premises. Country Disposal Clean-Up week can be viewed here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZONE 1 – JUNE 15-19, 2015 (SEE MAP)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;North&lt;/strong&gt; of 13th Street, Creston, Sherwood &amp;amp; Linne Roads&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZONE 2 – JUNE 22-26, 2015 (SEE MAP)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;South&lt;/strong&gt; of 13th Street, Creston, Sherwood &amp;amp; Linne Roads&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/media/2015cleanup_map.png&#34; alt=&#34;Annual Cleanup Map &#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commercial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/commercial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 09:37:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/commercial/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;bin-sizes:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;Bin Sizes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can choose from the following container sizes: 1.5-yard, 2-yard, 3-yard, and 4-yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;frequency-of-service:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;Frequency of Service&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may choose to have your containers emptied from once to six times per week. Saturday service is only available on 3 and 4-yard containers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recycling:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;Recycling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have three main recycling programs all of which are available to our customers at no additional charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-recycle-at-your-business:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;WHY RECYCLE AT YOUR BUSINESS?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recycling is an environmentally sound choice and it will save your business money. By effectively recycling you will be able to reduce the volume of materials that are placed in your garbage dumpster. Since our pricing structure is based on the size/frequency of only your garbage service there is an excellent economic advantage to recycling any and all materials that are recyclable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-commercial-recycling-programs-do-we-offer:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;WHAT COMMERCIAL RECYCLING PROGRAMS DO WE OFFER?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436553156497_306&#34;&gt;&lt;strong id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436553156497_305&#34;&gt;1. Commingle &#34;single stream&#34; recycling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;Using this program you are able to mix all of your non-organic recyclables in a single container. This is the most efficient way for us to collect recyclables from your business because a single truck will come to service this container that may have dozens of different recyclable materials in it. All materials are transferred to a recycling processor where they are sorted for recycling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;We&#39;ve found that most businesses greatly benefit from this service. Your employees don&#39;t need to waste time sorting materials. Also, this is the same type of recycling service that most people have at their homes and all of the same materials are accepted so educating your employees to fully participate in the recycling program at your business takes less effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Container sizes available:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;96-gallon automated cart&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1.5-yard split-bin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-yard split-bin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-yard bin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-yard bin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; 1.5 and 2-yard service is provided in a split-bin and must be matched with the same size garbage service because the bin is literally split in half.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;We are happy to provide your business with assistance in developing a recycling plan as well as helping you determine if your waste is recyclable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;Sample materials that can be discarded in the commingled recycling bin: office paper, plastic, metal items, cans, bottles, glass, boxes, packaging, envelopes, magazines, newspaper.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436553369915_337&#34;&gt;&lt;strong id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436553369915_336&#34;&gt;2. Source separated cardboard recycling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;You will be given a container specifically for your cardboard. We generally only offer this service to &#34;high volume&#34; cardboard generators and ask that if you only generate a small amount of cardboard that you mix it with other recyclables that your business has by using our commingle recycling service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Container size&amp;nbsp;available:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;3-yard&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436553369915_396&#34;&gt;&lt;strong id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436553369915_395&#34;&gt;3. Organics recycling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;With this service you can recycle all of your organic recyclable materials (no food waste just yet). This is a great service if you have landscaping that is maintained at your business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left:40px&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Container size&amp;nbsp;available: &lt;/strong&gt;96-gallon automated carts (we will give you several if needed)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in adding any of these services, please &lt;a href=&#34;http://paso-waste-site.squarespace.com/contact-us&#34;&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; our office and we will have your additional container(s) delivered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;container-placement:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;Container Placement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We require that your container is placed on a cement pad with easy access. Often businesses prefer to have their container placed inside of an enclosure. A representative can be sent to your location to discuss the placement of your container as well as provide you with assistance on designing either a pad or an enclosure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;rates:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;Rates&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-lg&#34; data-toggle=&#34;modal&#34; data-target=&#34;#myModal&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436547376749_938&#34;&gt;
  Rates
&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;container-cleaning:6bb28760d9618c0b43e7f2efea3ea43c&#34;&gt;Container Cleaning&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can request to have you containers steam cleaned twice per year. Any additional cleanings will be billed to your account. To schedule a cleaning please contact our office.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rent A Bin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/Rent-A-Bin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 12:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/Rent-A-Bin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;These bins are handy anytime you are doing a project that will generate a larger volume of trash than you can put in your automated container. Please call our office several days ahead of time to schedule your delivery as availability is limited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;bin-sizes:7e1a9aa362a04cea71a88e29b958d579&#34;&gt;Bin Sizes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left: 40px;&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436557289457_312&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:19px&#34; id=&#34;yui_3_17_2_1_1436557289457_311&#34;&gt;We offer temporary 3- and 4-yard bins to all of our customers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-yard  &lt;strong&gt;6&amp;rsquo;9&amp;rdquo; wide&lt;/strong&gt; x &lt;strong&gt;4&amp;rsquo;4&amp;rdquo; high&lt;/strong&gt; x &lt;strong&gt;4&amp;rsquo; deep&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-yard  &lt;strong&gt;6&amp;rsquo;9&amp;rdquo; wide&lt;/strong&gt; x &lt;strong&gt;4&amp;rsquo;4&amp;rdquo; high&lt;/strong&gt; x &lt;strong&gt;5&amp;rsquo;6&amp;rdquo; deep&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;rates:7e1a9aa362a04cea71a88e29b958d579&#34;&gt;Rates&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-yard  &lt;strong&gt;$70.64&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-yard  &lt;strong&gt;$84.51&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We charge rent of $2.00 per day after the first 10 days excluding the day of delivery and removal.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;service-agreement:7e1a9aa362a04cea71a88e29b958d579&#34;&gt;Service Agreement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We require that you fill out a service agreement prior to the delivery of your container. Please call our office and we will mail/fax/email you a copy: (805) 238-2381.
Some foooooooter content!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll-Off</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/rolloff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 09:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/paso-waste/service/rolloff/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>